I, for example,
am still afraid to defend my rights,
because initially the approach
to me, to my rights,
was severely violated. That is,
well, everything,
everything, that is,
lawyers tell me there
that the police can detain
you for only three hours,
and only for certain reasons,
but not for
passing the military medical commission.
That is, and the medical commission, by the way,
is also conducted in such a way
that basically even
very sick people turn out to be
fit or fit with limitations
but basically I saw there later
already in service quite sick
people with back problems, low
hemoglobin - that's when a person
can simply lose
consciousness, or back problems - that
is, a person regularly needs
to be injected with some
medications well to well to
function normally, and there
we have to run in body armor
which is very bad for the back.
They tell you that well you
try not to jump too high
and forward. That is
You follow me for the fact
that I can throw something out and so on,
but even just speak on my own behalf
I cannot,
Because if they start
looking for me hard,
they will find me quickly.
And if they find me,
they won't imprison me,
they won't even put me
in jail,
they'll just shove me into some
hellhole,
where I won't be able to make a peep,
or say anything,
and in the end everything for me could
turn out badly.
Without doing anything
illegal I already ended up in
these "Dubki" and well it's just like
such a place I don't know like there
among the residents
there are ex-convicts, there are
some very sick people
that is it could be
tuberculosis AIDS or with this like
nobody deals with it.
This greatly upsets, for example,
us. Well, there,
when I was there.
Because, well,
it's very bad to sit
next to a homeless person,
who just has soiled
pants.
That's it. That is,
what diseases he has. We, damn,
are forced to eat together
with these people. They feed us there.
That's it. Like that. That is...
This is the most severe violation
that was committed
against me.
That is, then they transferred me
to training camp,
and the training camp is like
considered good.
And there were already normal people,
you could talk to them,
they gave you a phone there,
there was some human
attitude.
Although they also detain you there,
that is, you can't,
well,
you don't have a phone in your hands.
you are limited in communication,
but there they give you the phone more often and there
it's like more humane
treatment. There people are already like,
there are no homeless people,
there are no seizures and I
was re-examined there like light
medical examinations I underwent
when I got to them.
Basically they practically
weren't bothered by anything,
some couple of spikes
on the cardiogram,
well they said like it'll do.
Since I myself haven't
been examined for a long time,
haven't undergone any treatments,
that is, I don't really know
how much my heart
is in order.
Because when they roughly
speaking caught me,
I literally had
"my heart sink."
That is, it really started to hurt.
Well, those are the stories.
Just further all kinds of different
things can happen to a person.
For example, Dima really,
it seems,
was much less lucky both
with the training camp and with this.
Because I was in Mykolaiv,
they gave me visits,
relatives came to see me.
They passed me all sorts of
treats or needed things:
headphones,
underwear and such.
Although, basically,
the uniform was already issued and there
basically everything was enough.